monastery: n.   寺院，修道院
Lesonate, a famous monastery, the great street Bernard Pass connects Switzerland to Italy.
著名的修道院Lesonate，大街Bernard Pass将瑞士连接到意大利。
pass: n.   关隘
At 2,473 meters, it is the highest mountain pass in Europe.
它是2473米的，是欧洲最高的山通行证。
monastery: n.   寺院，修道院
The famous monastery of St. Bernard, which was founded in 11th century, lies about a mile away.
著名的圣伯纳德修道院成立于11世纪，位于大约一英里外。
pass: n.   关隘
For hundreds of years, St. Bernard dogs have saved the lives of travelers crossing the dangerous pass.
数百年来，圣伯纳德的狗挽救了越过危险通行证的旅行者的生命。
watchdog: n.   看门狗
These friendly dogs, which were first brought from Asia, were used as watchdogs even in Roman times.
这些友好的狗最初是从亚洲带来的，即使在罗马时代也被用作看门狗。
pass: n.   关隘
Now that a tunnel has been built through the mountains, the pass is less dangerous.
现在，已经通过山脉建造了隧道，通行证危险不大。
But each year, the dogs are still sent out into the snow whenever a traveler is in difficulty.
但是每年，每年旅行者都遇到困难时，狗仍然会被送入雪中。
pass: n.   关隘, rashly: adj. 莽撞地，冒失地
Despite the new tunnel, there are still a few people who rashly attempt to cross the pass on foot.
尽管有新的隧道，但仍有一些人轻率地试图步行越过通行证。
monastery: n.   寺院，修道院
During the summer months, the monastery is very busy, for it is visited by thousands of people
在夏季，修道院很忙，因为成千上万的人拜访了修道院
pass: n.   关隘
who cross the pass in cars. As there are so many people about, the dogs have to be kept in a special
谁越过汽车。由于有很多人，必须将狗放在一个特别的地方
monastery: n.   寺院，修道院, enclosure: n.   围场，圈地
enclosure. In winter, however, life at the monastery is quite different. The temperature drops to
外壳。然而，在冬天，修道院的生活完全不同。温度下降到
pass: n.   关隘, monk: n.   和尚
30 oh and very few people attempt to cross the pass. The monks prefer winter to summer
30哦，很少有人试图越过通行证。僧侣喜欢冬天而不是夏天
privacy: n.   清静，隐居
if they have more privacy. The dogs have greater freedom. Two, for they are allowed to wander outside
如果他们有更多的隐私。狗有更大的自由。两个，因为他们被允许在外面徘徊
monastery: n.   寺院，修道院, enclosure: n.   围场，圈地, skier: n.   滑雪者
their enclosure. The only regular visitors to the monastery in winter are parties of skiers who go
他们的外壳。冬季唯一的普通游客是滑雪者的聚会
Easter: n.   复活节
there at. Christmas and Easter, these young people, who love the peace of mountains,
在那里。圣诞节和复活节，这些热爱山脉和平的年轻人，
monastery: n.   寺院，修道院
always receive a warm welcome at St. Bernard's monastery.
总是在圣伯纳德修道院受到热烈欢迎。